greenopolis.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Greenopolis

**PRIVACY POLICY**

PLEASE REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF SERVICE FOR THE SITE CAREFULLY. YOUR USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO SUCH PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF SERVICE. 

WM Organic Growth, Inc. ("WMOG," "we", "our" or "us") maintains the site located at the domain greenopolis.com ("Site"). This Privacy Policy describes the types of information collected from you, what we do with it, with whom we share it, and how you can correct or change such information. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy carefully, especially before providing any Personal Information through the Site. This Site is operated in and controlled from the United States of America. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or Site please contact us at the address at the end of this policy.   
**Types of Information Collected**   
Personally Identifiable Information ("Personal Information") is any information that can be used to identify a specific individual, such as your name, email address, home address, phone number and credit card information. This Site collects Personal Information when you interact with certain features of the Site; for example, when you subscribe for newsletters; register for membership services such as chat rooms or message boards; participate in chat rooms, blogs or other user forums; respond to polls or surveys; purchase merchandise via the Site; register for sweepstakes, contests and other promotional opportunities; or seek help from our customer service departments. We may also obtain Personal Information from reputable third parties, such as credit agencies.  
Non-Personal Information is information that does not identify you specifically, including data collected automatically through the operation of the Site. We may collect site usage data (such as which Site pages you visit and in what sequence) through the use of various technologies. For example, we collect IP addresses from individuals who visit the Site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that "serve up" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a page from a website, its servers log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to any Personal Information, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to us and the Site.   
We may also collect password information from you when you log in, as well as computer and connection information such as browser type or version. During some visits, we may use software tools, such as Javascript, to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, time spent on certain pages, page interaction information, and methods used to browse away from the page.  
**Member Profiles**   
Greenopolis.com is an online adult social networking community that allows people to connect by communicating, sharing and making new friends. To accomplish this, members create their own profiles, which contain the Personal Information that the members choose to include. This information may include such things as: first name or first and last name; gender; age; marital status; location (e.g., street, city, zip code); education level, and birthday. The information included in a member's profile will be shown to the people the member chooses. Each member will have certain choices related to the level of sharing when creating his/her profile, including: Personal image, Address, Latitude, Longitude, Languages spoken, Gender, Occupation, Children, Education, Marital Status, Birth-date and Contact information.  
PLEASE NOTE THAT, REGARDLESS OF WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION A MEMBER CHOOSES TO INCLUDE IN HIS OR HER PROFILE, OR WHAT LEVEL OF SHARING HE OR SHE CHOOSES, CERTAIN INFORMATION ABOUT EACH MEMBER WILL BE INCLUDED IN THAT MEMBER'S "PUBLIC PROFILE," WHICH IS AN ABBREVIATED VERSION OF A GREENOPOLIS PROFILE. (For example, the public profile may include, without limitation, the following: Member Since:, Last time logged on, Anything the user writes in the "About Me", The users friends, Their groups, their friends). PUBLIC PROFILES WILL BE AVAILABLE TO ANY USER OF GREENOPOLIS.COM, WHETHER OR NOT THE USER IS A MEMBER.  
**Message Boards, Chat Rooms, Blogs and Other User Forums**   
Please remember that information posted to message boards, chat rooms, blogs and other user forums becomes public information. Use caution when posting. Individuals under the age of 18 should be especially careful not to provide any personally identifiable information when participating in any area of the Site where postings might become public. Please see our Terms of Service for the standards of behavior that must be followed when using these portions of the Site.  
**Invitations to Friends**   
Greenopolis.com members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. We store the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. We do not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders. Recipients of invitations from Greenopolis.com may contact us at [cancel@greenopolis.com](mailto:cancel@greenopolis.com) to request the removal of their information from our database.   
Members may also store email addresses of people they know in their internal greenopolis.com address book and may also choose to send invitations and other communications to those addresses.  
You may prevent greenopolis.com email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by sending a single email with the subject "BLOCK" to [privacy@greenopolis.com](mailto:privacy@greenopolis.com). Please note that the email must come from the account you wish to block.   
**Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies**   
Like many sites, we use "cookies" or other similar technologies to collect non-Personal Information. A cookie is a small data file that writes to your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit the Site. Cookies allow the Site to measure traffic activity on the Site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, allowing you to visit "member only" portions of the Site without re-registering, and tracking the progress and number of entries in activities that require registration or entry, such as sweepstakes. Similarly, if you have asked us to send you information about upcoming products and promotions, using cookies we collect information about which Site pages you have visited and in what order ("Clickstream Data") that may allow us to narrow or limit the materials provided to you based on your prior online activities or preferences. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent, but it is possible that some parts of the Site will not function properly if you do so.  
In addition, we may use a service that collects data remotely by using so-called "pixel tags," "web beacons," "clear GIFs" or similar means (collectively, "Pixel Tags") embedded in the Site's content. A Pixel Tag is an electronic image, often a single pixel (1x1), that is ordinarily not visible to Site visitors and may be associated with cookies on the visitors' hard drives. This information is non-Personal Information.  
**Our Use of Your Data**   
We will use your Personal Information for the purposes for which it was provided. For example, if you provide Personal Information to register for a newsletter, to enter a contest or a sweepstake, or to purchase goods or services, we will use it to register you for or provide you with those goods or services. We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with information about features, services and other offerings that may be of interest to you. We also may send information or offers to selected groups of Site users on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give those businesses your name or address. Under certain circumstances (for example if you win a contest) we may post your Personal Information on the Site. We will notify you of this possibility when you provide the Personal Information and, if possible, when the Personal Information is posted.  
Cookies and similar tools may be used to relate your use of the Site and non-Personal Information to Personal Information obtained from you. If any non-Personal Information is linked with Personal Information, the linked non-Personal Information will then be treated as Personal Information.  
We may also use Personal Information in aggregate form for purposes of research or analysis. In order to better understand and serve the users of the Site, Greenopolis.com often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on Personal Information we gather. Although this aggregated data may be based in part on Personal Information, it does not identify you personally. Greenopolis.com may share this type of non-Personal Information with a variety of third parties, including its affiliates, agents, and current and prospective business partners.  
We may use non-Personal Information collected from the Site for site administration, advertising and promotional purposes, and we may share such information with various affiliated and unaffiliated entities for such purposes. For example, IP addresses are used for the purposes of system administration and to provide Non-Personal Information to advertisers about the volume of use on the Site, and Clickstream Data and demographic Non-Personal Information may be shared with our advertisers and business partners. We may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess technology that allows the Site to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on the Site. This data (including Clickstream Data about your activities on our Site) may be shared with these companies for this purpose.  
**Disclosure of Personal Information**   
We reserve the right to share Personal Information with our affiliates. If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with our affiliated companies for their marketing purposes, you may opt-out of such sharing by contacting us at [unsubscribe@greenopolis.com](mailto:unsubscribe@greenopolis.com) (see "Your Choices" below).  
We, like many businesses, sometimes hire other companies to perform certain business-related functions on our behalf such as hosting specific portions of the Site, maintaining databases, administering contests, mailing information and processing payments. When we employ a third party to perform these functions, that third party will only be provided with the particular Personal Information it needs to perform its function, and is required to protect the Personal Information. With your consent, we may also share Personal Information with pre-screened third parties for their marketing or promotional purposes. We will provide you with an opportunity to elect or decline these services or opportunities (see "Your Choices" below). In the event you have elected to "unsubscribe" from any of our services, we will share your Personal Information with third parties with whom we jointly offer such services solely to the extent necessary to ensure that your request not to receive such communications is honored. In addition, for third-party sponsored sweepstakes, contests or promotions, we may request Personal Information from you that may be shared with the sponsor upon request.  
In addition, we may disclose Personal Information without providing you with a choice under the following limited circumstances to: (1) protect the legal rights, privacy or safety of WM Organic Growth, or its subsidiaries, affiliates or its or their employees, agents and contractors; (2) protect the safety and security of visitors to our web sites or other properties; (3) protect against fraud or other illegal activity or for risk management purposes; (4) respond to inquiries or requests from public authorities; (5) permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; (6) enforce our Terms of Service; or (7) comply with the law or legal process.  
If we sell all or part of this Site or make a sale or transfer of assets or are otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, we may, in our sole discretion, transfer, sell or assign your Personal Information to a third party as part of or in connection with that transaction. Upon such transfer, the Privacy Policy of the acquiring entity may govern the further use of your Personal Information.  
**Third-Party Advertising and Links to Other Sites**   
This Site may include third-party advertising. These third party advertisers, or the Internet advertising companies that work on their behalf, may use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our Site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, Javascript, Pixel Tags and other technologies to deliver advertisements, collect information about the effectiveness of their advertisements, and to collect anonymous information about your visits to the Site, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other Personal Information). For more information about these specialized cookies and other technologies, and how to "opt out" of information collection by these companies, we suggest you visit <http://doubleclick.net/privacy_policy> or <http://networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>.   
Please note that this Site contains links to other sites that will not follow the same Privacy Policy as our Site. For instance, clicking on an advertisement or on links or other elements on the Site may take you to an entirely different site. Links to other sites may use our Site logo or style as a result of a co-branding agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you and may collect data and make use of that data in ways that this Site would not. Once you've left this Site, this Privacy Policy will no longer apply to Personal Information or any other data collected from or provided by you. You should check the applicable privacy policy to determine how that site will handle such data.  
**Your Choices**   
You can use the Site without providing any Personal Information, but if you decline to provide Personal Information, you may not be able to use certain services or features. If you have previously provided Personal Information to the Site and have subscribed to one or more email newsletters or are receiving emails or other communications from the Site and you do not want to receive such emails, please discontinue your subscriptions by clicking the "unsubscribeunsubscribe@greenopolis.com" link at the bottom of any message and emailing us with your unsubscribe request, or login to your Greenopolis.com profile page, select Settings to update your notification preferences. If you ask that we stop using your Personal Information, we will honor that request. However we will retain records of your Personal Information as needed in order to comply with applicable federal, state, or local law.  
**Access and Correction**   
If you would like to review, correct or change the Personal Information that you have previously provided us, please go to the "My Account" section of the web site when you are logged in or contact us at [info@greenopolis.com](mailto:info@greenopolis.com). We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Information in our possession.  
**Data Security Disclaimer**   
We have instituted physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to store and maintain Personal Information in a secure environment. For example, when highly confidential information, such as a credit card number, is transmitted through the Site, it is encrypted by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software. You may also be required to use a password to access certain pages on the Site where certain types of your information can be changed or deleted. It is therefore important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password, emails we may send you and to your computer. You take full responsibility for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. Although we take reasonable security precautions to secure the Personal Information that you choose to provide against the loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorized access of such information, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of greenopolis.com to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any Personal Information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. If you believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify us of the problem by contacting us at [info@greenopolis.com](mailto:info@greenopolis.com).  
**Exclusions**   
This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to greenopolis.com on or through this Site. All such Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential, and WMOG shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.  
**Other Terms and Conditions**   
Your access to and use of this Site is subject to the Terms of Service.  
**Applicable Law**   
We control and operate this Site from the United States. The Site is not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States. Please note that we do not represent or warrant that the Site is appropriate for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the Site do so at their own initiative and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules and regulations.   
**Changes to this Privacy Policy**   
From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives, changes in the law or technology, or changes in our practices regarding information collection and use. If we make revisions to the way we collect or use Personal Information, we may provide notice of those changes by either: (1) announcing the change on the home page of the Site or (2) taking such other action as we deem appropriate under the circumstances, including without limitation, posting the revised draft of this Privacy Policy on the Site. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the "Last Updated" legend at the top of this page. Any changes to this policy will become effective upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Internet, accessible through the Site. By continuing to use the Site following such changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or in part, please do not continue using this Site.  
**Contacting Greenopolis.com Regarding Your Privacy:**   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, Personal Information gathered by this Site, or about the operation of this Site, or if you wish to unsubscribe from the Site, please contact us at the email, or at the address listed below  
WM Organic Growth, Inc.  
1001 Fannin Street, Suite 4000  
Houston, Texas 77002  
Attention: Legal Department
